[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of demonic power is little Regan possessed by in the 1973 movie The Exorcist?", "correct_answer": "Satan", "incorrect_answers": ["Her dead fathers ghost", "Judas Iscariots spirit", "A legion of demons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aaliyahs character refers to Anthony Andersons character by what name in Romeo Must Die?", "correct_answer": "Moron", "incorrect_answers": ["Pinhead", "Dorkster", "Jerk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2008 film is a remake of the 2004 Filipino film Sigaw. Sigaw translates to shout or scream.", "correct_answer": "The Echo", "incorrect_answers": ["The Haunting", "Planet Terror", "Quarantine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the treatment and prevention of what medical condition is yogurt proven to be beneficial?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Gum disease", "Gastrointestinal conditions", "Obesity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alphonse Gabriel Capone, a.k.a. Al Capone, was a real American criminal who inspired many movie and book characters. How did the real Al Capone die?", "correct_answer": "Cardiac arrest", "incorrect_answers": ["From stroke", "He was shot.", "He was sentenced to death."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Greyhound is a cocktail which contains Tonic.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is an atom having the valance of 1 called?", "correct_answer": "Monad", "incorrect_answers": ["Nucleuid", "Mono particle", "Monotom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Squid and octopus are mollusks.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This was the largest active passenger airplane for 2007.", "correct_answer": "Airbus A380", "incorrect_answers": ["Sukhoi 27", "Boeing 757", "Boeing 747"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This large cat was is the result of crossbreeding between a domestic cat and a Jungle Cat.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Jungle Curl", "Chausie", "Mountain Cougar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which American actress received her 13th Academy Award nomination in 2003?", "correct_answer": "Meryl Streep", "incorrect_answers": ["Katherine Hepburn", "Joan Crawford", "Bette Davis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Sulfur?", "correct_answer": "S", "incorrect_answers": ["Sf", "Su", "Sl"]}]